<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<SBS_MAM_Job_List>
  <SBS_MAM_Job>
    <Job_Creation_Time>1700526581</Job_Creation_Time>
    <Job_Type>34</Job_Type>
    <Job_Src_Path_HR_Abs>E:\output_reuters\2023-11-20T235708Z_1_LWD974920112023RP1_RTRWNEV_D_9749-SOCCER-WORLDCUP-BRA-ARG-PREVIEW.mxf</Job_Src_Path_HR_Abs>
    <Job_Src_Path_HR>\2023-11-20T235708Z_1_LWD974920112023RP1_RTRWNEV_D_9749-SOCCER-WORLDCUP-BRA-ARG-PREVIEW.mxf</Job_Src_Path_HR>
    <Job_Src_ID>2023-11-20T235708Z_1_LWD974920112023RP1_RTRWNEV_D_9749-SOCCER-WORLDCUP-BRA-ARG-PREVIEW.MP4</Job_Src_ID>
    <Job_Src_App_Data>
      <PLAN_KEYWORD>#South America / Central America#Soccer#Sport#SVO#Latin#Sports#RIO DE JANEIRO, BRAZIL#Brazil#Soccer#sports#Brazil#Argentina#World Cup</PLAN_KEYWORD>
      <Story>
        <br />
        <br />VIDEO SHOWS: FOOTAGE OF BRAZILIAN SOCCER PLAYERS TRAINING / SOUNDBITES FROM BRAZILIAN COACH FERNANDO DINIZ / SOUNDBITE FROM PLAYER<br />RESENDING WITH COMPLETE STORY<br />SHOWS: RIO DE JANEIRO, BRAZIL (NOVEMBER 20, 2023) (REUTERS – Access all)<br />1. BRAZILIAN COACH FERNANDO DINIZ WALKING ON FIELD<br />2. VARIOUS OF DINIZ AND GOALKEEPER ALISSON BECKER TALKING BEFORE TRAINING SESSION <br />3. VARIOUS OF DINIZ TALKING WITH PRESIDENT OF BRAZILIAN SOCCER FEDERATION EDNALDO RODRIGUES<br />4. (SOUNDBITE) (Portuguese) BRAZILIAN COACH, FERNANDO DINIZ, SAYING:<br />    "Argentina's national team has been one of the best for a long time, not only because they won the World Cup. Argentina has players who play in the best leagues and stand out, as well as having Messi. It's a team that has played for a long time, had an incredibly successful cycle in the Copa America and the World Cup, and maintained a base. So, if it's not the best, it's among the three best football teams in the world today. So we are aware of that and will prepare the team to do our best against a great opponent."<br />5. VARIOUS OF PLAYERS DURING TRAINING SESSION <br />6. (SOUNDBITE) (Portuguese) BRAZILIAN COACH, FERNANDO DINIZ, SAYING:<br />    "Dealing with Messi is obviously different, and you have to worry. There is no way not to worry about a player of that magnitude with his decision-making power. We also have to play. We must not move away from our characteristics and at the same time try to contain all the creativity and decision-making that he has."<br />7. VARIOUS OF PLAYERS DURING TRAINING SESSION <br />8. PLAYERS WALKING ON FIELD<br />9. PLAYERS TRAINING <br />10. (SOUNDBITE) (Portuguese) BRAZILIAN SOCCER PLAYER, MARQUINHOS, SAYING:<br />    "Messi is a genius. He is a different player. Despite his age, he will always be doing great things. As a friend and teammate, I made the most of my time with him at PSG. I saw a lot of things from him, and I grew a lot in all aspects. But tomorrow, unfortunately, he is my opponent. So, I'm alerting my teammates as much as possible about what we can do to limit his actions in the game. We must know that he is a different player that we must be very careful of."<br />11. VARIOUS OF PLAYERS TRAINING <br />STORY: The fierce rivalry between Brazil and Argentina will hit fever pitch when Lionel Messi's world champions face the struggling hosts in a mouth-watering South American World Cup qualifying clash in Rio de Janeiro on Tuesday (November 21).<br />    Five-time World Cup winners Brazil will rely on their fans in a sold-out Maracana stadium to give them an extra boost to recover after losing back-to-back games in the qualifying competition for the first time in their history.<br />    As they struggle with injuries to key players like Neymar and Vinicius Jr, caretaker manager Fernando Diniz must resort to a young team against Argentina but one that he guarantees will stay true to Brazil's identity even against a great like Messi.<br />    Winless in the last three games, Brazil have dropped to fifth in the South American standings on seven points from five games after losing 2-1 to Colombia on Thursday. They are under heavy pressure as they prepare for long-time rivals Argentina, who top the standings on 12 points.<br />(Production: Sergio Queiroz, Liamar Ramos)<br />
      </Story>
      <OBJ_Origin_Abs>D:\agent_REUTERS\2023-11-20T235708Z_1_LWD974920112023RP1_RTRWNEV_D_9749-SOCCER-WORLDCUP-BRA-ARG-PREVIEW.MP4</OBJ_Origin_Abs>
      <OBJ_Origin>\2023-11-20T235708Z_1_LWD974920112023RP1_RTRWNEV_D_9749-SOCCER-WORLDCUP-BRA-ARG-PREVIEW.MP4</OBJ_Origin>
      <Script_Origin>D:\agent_REUTERS\2023-11-21T002852Z_4_RW974920112023RP1_RTRMADC_0_SOCCER-WORLDCUP-BRA-ARG-PREVIEW.XML</Script_Origin>
    </Job_Src_App_Data>
  </SBS_MAM_Job>
</SBS_MAM_Job_List>