<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<SBS_MAM_Job_List>
  <SBS_MAM_Job>
    <Job_Creation_Time>1700526659</Job_Creation_Time>
    <Job_Type>74</Job_Type>
    <Job_Src_ID>5383733_Soccer Brazil Preview_1_1080i60ESSENCE--cb1e1.mp4</Job_Src_ID>
    <Job_Src_Path_HR_Abs>E:\output_aptn\5383733_Soccer Brazil Preview_1_1080i60ESSENCE--cb1e1.mxf</Job_Src_Path_HR_Abs>
    <Job_Src_Path_LR_Abs>E:\output_aptn\5383733_Soccer Brazil Preview_1_1080i60ESSENCE--cb1e1\5383733_Soccer Brazil Preview_1_1080i60ESSENCE--cb1e1.mp4</Job_Src_Path_LR_Abs>
    <Job_Src_Path_CAT_Abs>E:\output_aptn\5383733_Soccer Brazil Preview_1_1080i60ESSENCE--cb1e1\5383733_Soccer Brazil Preview_1_1080i60ESSENCE--cb1e1_00000000.jpg</Job_Src_Path_CAT_Abs>
    <Job_Src_Path_HR>\5383733_Soccer Brazil Preview_1_1080i60ESSENCE--cb1e1.mxf</Job_Src_Path_HR>
    <Job_Src_Path_LR>\5383733_Soccer Brazil Preview_1_1080i60ESSENCE--cb1e1\5383733_Soccer Brazil Preview_1_1080i60ESSENCE--cb1e1.mp4</Job_Src_Path_LR>
    <Job_Src_Path_CAT>\5383733_Soccer Brazil Preview_1_1080i60ESSENCE--cb1e1\5383733_Soccer Brazil Preview_1_1080i60ESSENCE--cb1e1_00000000.jpg</Job_Src_Path_CAT>
    <Job_Dest_Path>//nds/storage/international</Job_Dest_Path>
    <Job_Dest_Filename>//nds/storage/international</Job_Dest_Filename>
    <Job_STT_Enable>False</Job_STT_Enable>
    <Job_translation_Enable>True</Job_translation_Enable>
    <Job_OBJ_CATEGORY_ID>2010068</Job_OBJ_CATEGORY_ID>
    <Job_OBJ_CATEGORY_DESC>aptn</Job_OBJ_CATEGORY_DESC>
    <Job_Src_App_Data>
      <Title>5383733_Soccer Brazil Preview</Title>
      <PLAN_KEYWORD>#FIFA World Cup#Soccer#Sports#Physical fitness#Athlete injuries#Colombia#South America#Brazil#South America#Argentina#South America#Fernando Diniz#Marquinhos#Marquinhos#Gabriel Jesus#Lionel Messi#Real Madrid</PLAN_KEYWORD>
      <Story>
        <br />
        <br />Editors / Producers please click to view this video on 
<br />
        <br />
        <br />Marquinhos - 'Messi is a genius' and Brazil must be 'very careful' in stopping him
<br />Editors / Producers please click to view this video on 
<br />
        <br />
        <br />SHOTLIST:
<br />RESTRICTIONS: Use on broadcast and digital channels, including social. Available worldwide. Can be used for the duration of your current contract. No takedown necessary for stand alone digital users. All usage subject to rights licensed in contract. For any questions regarding rights restrictions please contact planning@sntv.com
<br />Canarinha's Training Camp, Rio De Janeiro, Brazil. 20th November 2023.
<br />1. 00:00 SOUNDBITE (Portuguese): Marquinhos, Brazil defender:
<br />(About the threat posed by Argentina's star forward Lionel Messi)
<br />"(Lionel) Messi is a genius. He is a genius, a differential player. Despite his age (36-years-old), he is always going to do great things. So, as a friend and a former team-mate, I really enjoyed the time he was there at Paris Saint-Germain (between 2021-2023). I saw a lot from him. I have enjoyed growing a lot with him and in all aspects. But tomorrow (Tuesday), unfortunately, we are on different side and I am discussions with my Brazilian team-mates to try to find out what we can do in order to nullify him... That would not be the right word. But to try to take away more and more of his actions inside the game. Knowing that he is a special player, we have to be very careful and that a lot of the Argentina national team's passages of play go directly through him. So, he is a great player, he is a genius and we have to be very careful tomorrow (Tuesday). We have to be aware that he is a special player, we have to be very careful and we have to be aware that a lot of Argentina's attacks go directly through him. So, I repeat, he is a great player, he is a genius and we have to be very careful tomorrow (Tuesday)." 
<br />2. 00:57 SOUNDBITE (Portuguese): Fernando Diniz, Brazil interim head coach:
<br />(About Brazil's World Cup qualifying match against rivals Argentina)
<br />"I hope we can have a great game, that we can score very well. We know that they (Argentina) are a team of great quality, with one of the greatest players in history (Lionel Messi), who is still building his beautiful story. And we have prepared a lot for the game. I hope we have a great match and that the (Brazil) fans - because of what they see on the pitch - are able to play along with the team, and that will then be reciprocated further by our players, in the form of effective performances."
<br />3. 01:26 Wide of the training pitch in foggy conditions
<br />4. 01:33 Wide of Brazil players entering the training pitch
<br />5. 01:42 Gabriel Jesus and Endrick enter the training pitch
<br />6. 01:49 Brazil players during ball juggling exercises as a group before the start of training
<br />7. 02:00 Wide of Brazil players during warm-up exercises in small groups in training
<br />8. 02:08 Various of Brazil players during stretching and warm-up exercises in small groups in training
<br />9. 02:19 Close of Brazil players during stretching and warm-up exercises in small groups in training
<br />10. 02:26 Wide of Brazil players getting ready for the start of a new training drill
<br />11. 02:32 Brazil players during 'rondo' exercises in training
<br />12. 02:41 Brazil interim head coach Fernando Diniz talking to one of his coaching staff during training
<br />13. 02:50 Various of Brazil players during 'rondo' exercises in training
<br />14. 03:07 Marquinhos attempting to win the ball back during 'rondo' exercises in Brazil training, and camera pan to another group of players
<br />15. 03:20 Brazil players taking a drinks break during training
<br />16. 03:31 Fernando Diniz (left) talking to Brazil goalkeeper Alisson Becker (right) during training
<br />SOURCE: SNTV
<br />DURATION: 03:37
<br />STORYLINE:
<br />Brazil continued their preparations on Monday, a day before their pivotal 2026 FIFA World Cup qualifier against fierce rivals and defending world champions Argentina, which will take place at the Maracana in Rio de Janeiro.
<br />Since taking over from Tite, Fernando Diniz has overseen a difficult CONMEBOL World Cup qualifying campaign for the 'Selecao', with Brazil having taken just seven points from a possible 15, which included a 2-1 defeat to a Luis Diaz-inspired Colombia last time out.
<br />On the other hand, their next opponents - Lionel Messi's Argentina - sit top of the 10-team qualifying section with four wins from five matches.
<br />To make matters worse, Brazil lost star forward Vinicius Jr. to a hamstring injury in the first-half of that defeat to Colombia, and the Real Madrid attacker is expected to be out for around two-and-a-half months.
<br />Joao Pedro was introduced as Vinicius Jr.'s replacement in that game and the Brighton forward could now potentially come in for a start against Argentina, but it seems more likely that Gabriel Martinelli - who scored against Colombia - will feature in attack.
<br />Endrick, who is joining Real Madrid next year, debuted against Colombia and the 17-year-old is expected to again play a part in the final third of the field, while Martinelli's Arsenal team-mate Gabriel Jesus is back in training following a hamstring issue and could be on the bench.
<br />Meanwhile, Aston Villa's Douglas Luiz could potentially be introduced to strengthen the midfield alongside Andre and Bruno Guimaraes.
<br />Brazil have a number of notable absentees, with Ederson, Danilo, Eder Militao, Casemiro, Neymar and Richarlison among those unavailable for selection due to various fitness problems.
</Story>
      <OBJ_Origin_Abs>D:\agent_APTN\5383733_Soccer Brazil Preview_1_1080i60ESSENCE--cb1e1.mp4</OBJ_Origin_Abs>
      <OBJ_Origin>\5383733_Soccer Brazil Preview_1_1080i60ESSENCE--cb1e1.mp4</OBJ_Origin>
      <OBJ_Duration>217.784229</OBJ_Duration>
    </Job_Src_App_Data>
  </SBS_MAM_Job>
</SBS_MAM_Job_List>